Ada Peirce McCormick papers, 1881-1978 (bulk 1920-1974)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: General Files, ca. 1915-1978
  - Rinehart, and Co. 1950-1953 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Robert, Eleanor S. 1937-1938 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Roberts, David. 1949-1951 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Robins, Raymond and Margaret. 1945-1947 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, Carol. 1950-1952 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Robinson, Earl (song of the United Nations). 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Robinson, Ione. 1957-1967 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller, Godfrey. 1943-1945 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Rodeo. 1946 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Rogers, John William. 1946 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Rogers, Katherine. 1948 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Rollins, Leighton and Catherine Snow. 1941-1971 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Romine, Ray. 1950-1952 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor. 1932-1961 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. 1942 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Kermit. 1943 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Roosevelt, Mrs. Theodore, Jr. 1943 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Rosensteil, Lewis and David. 1943-1968 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Rosenstock-Huessy, Dr. Eugen. 1938-1939 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Ross, Dr. Emory. 1948-1953 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Ross, Myrtyl. 1948-1949 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Routledge and Kegan Paul. 1950-1952 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Roy, Dean Francis. 1957-1970 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Rufenacht, Mrs. R.E. 1953-1966 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Rushing, Marie Morris. 1951 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Russell, A.E., drawing by APM. ca. 1930s (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Russell, Regis D. 1949 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Russell Sage Foundation. 1947-1954 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Russo, Lola. 1950 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - S: Miscellaneous. 1937-1971 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Sagendorph, Robb. 1943-1973 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Saint Anne's Convalescent Home for Children. 1940-1958 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Saint Benedict's House. 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Saint John's College. 1967-1972 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Saint John's Episcopal Church. 1936-1961 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Saint Joseph's Hospital. 1963-1971 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Saint Margaret's Convent. 1934-1975 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Saint Paulls Memorial Parish Church. 1959-1970 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Salter, Katherine Hayden (Friend of Margaret Sanger). 1943 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Saltus, Carol. 1958-1962 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Salvatore, Victor and Nell (Ryerson). 1943-1967 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Sambrot, William. 1948 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Sample, Charles. 1950 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Samuel, Maurice. 1951 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Sanborn, Eleanor B., (Fred McCormick's niece). 1936-1966 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Sanger, Dr. Stuart. 1948-1961 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Sanger, Margaret. 1934-1970 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Saqui, Mrs. L. Lubin. 1943-1944 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Sargent, Porter. 1945-1947 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Sarton, George. 1942-1958 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Saturday Evening Post. 1942-1950 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Saturday Review of Literature. 1943-1957 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Saunders, Cecelia. 1944-1958 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Saunders, Mrs. Maurice. 1941-1945 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Save the Children Federation. 1949-1951 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Sayre, Mildred. 1945-1946 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Scaife, Mrs. J. Verner. 1944-1960 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Schaffer, Enos and Pauline. 1943-1958 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Schantz, Adam. 1946-1947 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Schenley Distilleries. 1946 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Schereschewsky, Caroline. 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Schevill, Margaret. 1943 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Schillo, Marian. 1945-1946 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Schlabach Bill, Wisconsin. 1947 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Schmucker, Walter Jr. 1949-1950 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Schnable, George and Sylvia. 1965 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Schneck, Dr. Matthew M.R. 1934-1950 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Schoonmaker, Mrs. Nancy. 1929-1930 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Schultz, Dr. William. 1957 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Schuman, Henry (publishers). 1950-1953 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Schurz (Carl) Memorial Foundation. 1943-1951 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Schweitzer, Albert. re: promotions about. 1946-1965 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, Educational Foundation. 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, Fellowship. 1948-1961 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Schweitzer, Albert, Festival. 1950-1951 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Sci-Art Publishers. 1950 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Science. 1949-1952 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Science Fair, University of Arizona. 1955 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Science Fair, University of Arizona. 1956 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Science Fair, Univeristy of Arizona. 1957 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Science Fair, University of Arizona. 1958 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Science Fair, Univeristy of Arizona. 1959 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Science Fair, Univeristy of Arizona. 1960-1969 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Science of Mind Magazine. 1946-1947 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Scott, Reverend Lee. 1959-1969 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Scribner's (Charles) Sons. 1951-1958 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Scripps-Howard. 1959 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Seamen's church Institute of New York. 1940-1960 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Seattle Chamber of Commerce. 1943 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Seaver, Reverend George. 1957-1962 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Sedgwick, R. Minturen. 1954-1970 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Segura, Caltofen. 1948-1949 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Selincourt, Huge de. 1948 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Selway, Reverend George. 1961 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Sen, John J. 1950 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Senna, Manuel P. 1966 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Seventeen Magazine. 1945-1947 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Seymour, Mrs. Augustus T. 1943-1958 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Shantz, Dr. and Mrs. Homer L. 1930-1958 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Sharp, Charles. 1946 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Shaw, George Bernard. 1957-1960 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Sheed and Ward. 1948-1972 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Sheed, Frank and Maizie Ward. 1964 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Shelters for Defense. 1961 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Sherwood, Katherine. 1946-1947 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Shipler, Dr. Guy Emery. 1942 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Sholin, Reverend Paul David. 1948-1972 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Short Creek, Arizona, Mormons. 1954 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Shrine of the Ages, Arizona, Grand Canyon. 1955-1959 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Shun, Ivan N. 1942 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Shuster, George N. 1950-1957 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Sigma Xi. 1952-1963 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Simley, Dr. O.A. 1949-1960 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Sinclair, Murray. 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Singh, Charan. 1943-1950 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Singh, Dr. Anup. 1944-1946 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Sister Grace and other nuns. 1935-1970 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Sister M. Sylvie, Pare. 1971-1974 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Sisters of the Holy Nativity. 1937-1974 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Sisters of the Way of the Cross. 1940-1948 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Skeel, Emily. 1937-1952 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Sloane, William and Associates. 1951-1953 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Slocum, Burl and Esther. 1946-1961 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Small, William A. Jr. 1954 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Chard Powers. 1948 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Charlie. 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Smith, Chester. 1943-1951 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Kay Best. 1948-1955 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Lillian. 1937-1966 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Smith, Watson and Lucy. 1955-1973 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Snow, Edgar P. 1942-1945 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Servico Social. 1945 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Social activities of APM. 1950-1967 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Sokolsky, George. 1946-1954 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Solarsh, Jack, Aeroworker. 1943 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Solve, Dr. Melvin and Norma. 1943-1970 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Sonner, Augusta. 1943-1952 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Soong, T.V. 1942 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Soroptimist Club. 1947-1956 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Soss, Wilma. 1954-1961 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Sound-Chicago. 1949-1950 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - South American Embassy letters. 1949 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Southern Arizona Bank and Trust Co. 1946-1958 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Southern Arizona Livestock Association. 1968-1973 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Southside Virginia News. 1942 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Southwest Communications Control. 1949-1962 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Southwest Library Association. 1946 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Southwest Review Magazine. 1945-1948 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Sowerby, Fred and Ann. 1946-1972 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Spanish Treasure, Arizona, Tumacacori. 1953 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Speckter, Martin. 1946 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Speer, Emma Bailey (Mrs. Robert). 1944-1946 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Speiden, Jack. 1934-1956 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Spingarn, Lawrence V. 1944 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Spingarn, Steve. 1957 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Spoelstra, Helen Staton. 1944-1946 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Sponagle, James. 1948-1970 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Spurling, Caroline. 1946-1947 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Squier, Joel. 1946-1952 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Stace, Dr. Walter. 1955 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Stamm, Ruth. 1946 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Standard Business Service. 1957 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Standard Oil Co. 1945-1952 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Stangl, Jessie. 1945-1947 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - The Star. 1946-1970 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Steinheimer's Bookstore. 1946-1961 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Stephan, Ruth. 1946-1971 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Stern, Karl. 1963 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Stern, Mrs. Harold M. 1960-1963 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Stevens, Reverend F. 1943 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. 1952-1956 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Steward, Harold D. 1942-1944 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Stewart, Jean. 1965-1974 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Stimmler, Roland. 1949 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Stoetzner, Dr. Eric W. 1943-1944 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Stokes, Anson-Phelps (Phelps-Stokes fund). 1943-1946 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Strickler, Glen W. 1935-1968 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Stryker, Charlottee (Mrs. Julius). 1948-1957 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Student Religion Council. 1953-1960 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Student Religion Council. 1960-1968 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Student World. 1946-1951 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Subscription List (APM). 1957-1971 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Summers, Richard A. 1946-1969 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Sun, Mrs J.H. 1949 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Sun Yat Sen Group. 1932-1947 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Sunday Evening Forum. 1944-1968 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Sung-San (Chinese flyer Trained in Arizona). 1943-1945 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Survey Associates. 1942-1947 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Suttles, Shirley. 1946-1953 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Swift, Mrs. Simpson. 1944-1945 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Switzerland Legation. 1952 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Symington, Stuart. 1957 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Szold, Henrietta (founder of Hadassah). 1955-1961 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - T: Miscellaneous. 1941-1971 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Tallantyre, Renee. 1944-1946 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Tanaka, Itaru. 1952-1960 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Tappan, Dr. Paul. 1949-1950 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Taylor, Ann Richards. 1937-1968 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Taylor, Reverend Marry. 1945 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Taylor, Rosemary Drachman. 1945-1967 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Taylor, Sir Hugh. 1955-1974 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Telegrams. 1944-1967 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Teller, Sidney A. 1945-1947 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Terman, Dr. Lewis M. 1946-1952 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Terry, Lawrence. 1920-1971 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Terry, Stuart. 1949 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Theologia Moralis. 1943 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Thoburn (Isabella) College. 1948-1953 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Thompson, Dorothy. 1942-1961 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Thompson, Margaret (Cabot Chapel). 1945-1961 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Thompson, Margaret Williams. 1960-1971 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Thomson, O. Howard. 1943-1944 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Thrasher, Corrine. 1942-1948 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Thrasher, Edith. 1940-1954 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Thrift, Inez. 1950-1953 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Thum, F. Charles. 1948-1949 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Thurber, James. 1943-1951 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Thurman, Dr. Howard. 1945-1968 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Tide Magazine. 1943-1953 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Time Magazine. 1943-1955 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Tomorrow Magazine. 1943-1955 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Tong, Dr. Hollington. 1943 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Topping, Elizabeth. 1947-1948 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Tormey, Thomas. 1963-1973 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Travelers Insurance Co. 1952 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Treat, William W. 1967-1970 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Tremblay, Napoleon J. 1955-1961 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Trudelle, Beatrice G. 1946-1947 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Truman, Harry S. 1944-1949 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Tsiang, T.F. 1943 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Tucker, Leigh. 1951-1952 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Tucker, William John. 1946 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Tuller School. 1961 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Tuskegee Institute. 1946-1972 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Tucson Advertising Club. 1949-1974 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Tucson Adult Literacy Council. ca. 1968-1974 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Tucson Boys Chorus. 1945-1961 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Tucson Chamber of Commerce. 1941-1973 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Tucson Civic Chorus. 1954-1959 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Tucson Community Council. 1955-1965 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Tucson Community School. 1948-1959 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Tucson Council for Civic Unity. 1949-1960 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Tucson Daily Citizen. 1942-1969 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Tucson Ecumenical Council (Council of Churches). 1954-1968 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Tucson Ecumenical Council. 1968-1969 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Tucson Ecumenical Council. 1970-1974 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Tucson Festival Society. 1950-1959 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Tucson Fine Arts Association. 1949-1960 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Tucson Housing Foundation. 1965-1971 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Tucson Indian Training School. 1950 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Tucson Jewish community Council. 1950-1971 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Tucson Little Theater. 1945-1953 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Tucson Medical Center. 1945-1968 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Tucson Ministers Association. 1943-1965 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Tucson Peace Center. 1961-1967 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Tucson Press Club. 1948-1966 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Tucson Public Schools. 1947-1957 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Tucson Regional Plan. 1941, 1960 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Tucson Sunshine Climate Club. 1946-1958 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Tucson-Trikkala (Greece) Affiliation. 1949-1951 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Tucson Urban League. 1955 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Tucson Watercolor Guild. 1948-1950 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Tucson Writers' Club. 1948 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Tudor, Verna Moses. 1936-1971 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Tupper, Clara Tarbell. 1938-1949 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Turner, Margaret L. 1944-1948 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Twice a Year Magazine. 1943-1947 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - U: Miscellaneous. 1935-1960 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Udall, Morris K. 1955-1974 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Udall, Stewart. 1954-1961 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Union Now. 1939-1940 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Union Theological Seminary. 1951-1963 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - United Nations Association. 1946-1967 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - United Nations, formation. 1945-1950 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - United Nations World Magazine. 1947-1950 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - United States Department of Justice and FBI. 1947-1951 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - United States Department of State. 1942-1952 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - United States Post Office. 1946-1950 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - United States Senate. 1954 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - United World Federalists, National. 1946 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - United World Federalists, Tucson. 1947-1950 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Universities and Colleges, Miscellaneous. 1943-1955 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - University of Chicago. 1943-1950 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - University of Chicago Press. 1943-1948 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - University of Maine. 1960-1974 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - University of New Mexico Press. 1942-1948 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - University of Arizona, College of Medicine. 1964-1972 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - University of Arizona, College of Nursing. 1967-1973 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - University of Arizona, Presidents. 1943-1971 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - University of Arizona, Foundation and President's Club. 1967-1971 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - University of Arizona, gifts by APM. 1960-1971 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - University of Arizona, housing. 1967-1968 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - University of Arizona, Library. 1944-1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - University of Arizona, Medallion of Merit Award. 1960 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - University of Arizona, Miscellaneous. 1936-1969 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - University of Arizona, YMCA and YWCA. 1949 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Univeristy Pastors' Fellowship (UPF). 1947-1953 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - UPF. 1954-1957 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - UPF. 1958-1960 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - UPF. 1961 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - UPF. 1965-1966 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - UPF. 1967-1971 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - UPF. 1972-1974 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - UPF, Guide to Religious Organizations. 1959-1973 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - UPF, Inter-faith cooperation. 1955 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - UPF. Religion in Life Week. 1947-1963 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - UPF. religious centers of campus. 1960 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - UPF, student religious centers. 1955-1960 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Upshaw, Marie. 1968 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Urban, A.W. 1949-1953 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Urz, Margaret. 1952-1959 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - V: Miscellaneous. 1942-1967 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Vail, Alice. 1945-1967 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Valley National Bank. 1950-1972 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Valley National Bank building. 1943-1952 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Vance, Eleanor Graham. 1949 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Van Dusen, Dr. Henry P. 1951-1961 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Van Dyke, Henry. 1924-1926 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Van Etten, Reverend Dr. Edwin Jan (baptized APM). 1941-1955 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Van Hardeveld, Mrs. Rose. 1943-1949 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Van Waters, Dr. Miriam. 1949 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Vatican Ambassador. 1951-1952 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Vaughn, Frances Kennedy. 1947-1970 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Venezis, Elias. 1949 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Verde Valley School. 1948-1950 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Vernon, Dr. Ambrose White. 1928-1942 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - The Victory-La Victoria. 1945 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam, Arizona soldiers killed in. 1968-1970 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Viking Press. 1944-1969 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Villegas, Magda. 1943-1944 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Vistas. 1948, 1961 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Vogel, Reverend Joseph L. 1945-1948 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Von Isser, Josef and family. 1939-1972 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Vorse, Mary Heaton. 1943-1945 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - W: Miscellaneous. 1940-1972 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Waddell, Irma. 1946-1968 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Walgreen, Myrtle. 1954-1963 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Wall, Dr. James H. 1955-1966 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Wallace, Reverend Jerry. 1934-1970 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Wall Street Journal. 1954-1958 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Wallace, Mary Blair. 1938-1941 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Walls, Reverend Arthur. 1960-1961 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Walsh, Richard J. 1942-1947 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Ware, Harriet Webster. 1946-1972 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Watkins, David. 1952-1956 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Watson, Thomas J. 1947-1951 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Webster, Dr. Clara. 1955 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Weeks, Reverend and Mrs. William, Larry. 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Weil, Simone. 1945-1951 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Welles, Sumner. 1959 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Welty, Howard. 1942 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Wesley Foundation. 1958-1974 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - West, Anne. 1948-1956 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Wester, George K. 1944-1963 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Western Union. 1942-1954 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Western Ways. 1946-1951 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Whallon, Archer. 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Whipple, William. 1950-1951 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Whitaker, Marie. 1945-1949 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - White, Dr. Paul Dudley. 1958-1963 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - White, E.B. 1945-1952 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - White, Mrs. Joseph L. 1942-1949 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - White, William Allen. 1942-1944 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Whitlock-Rose, Dr. Elaine. 1916-1950 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Whitney, Harold. 1956 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Who's Who. 1943-1961 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Wiechert, Ernst. 1950-1952 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Wigman, Mary. (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Wilcox, Thomas. 1954-1958 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Wilder, Thornton. 1926-1971 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Wilder, Thornton, reminiscences. 1937-1938 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Wilder, Thornton, two books (in French, inscribed). (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Williams, J. Mack. 1945 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Wilson, Annette. 1950-1951 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Wilson, Bridget. 1951 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Wilson, Dr. Edwin B. 1952 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Wilson (H.W.) Co. 1943-1971 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Winn, Ada Pierce. 1930-1946 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Winship Family. 1943-1945 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Winston, Daoma. 1951 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Witham, Dr. Lois. 1946-1950 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Wolfe, Julia Whittier. 1951 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Women's Voluntary Services. 1941-1943 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Wood, Cornelius A. 1947 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Wood, Elizabeth Lambert. 1944-1956 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Wood, Leonard (Memorial Hospital). 1943-1947 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Woodin, William and Ann. 1935-1970 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Woods, Don. 1945 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Woods, Mrs. Arthur (Helen). 1941-1947 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Woodson, Carter Godwin. 1945-1946 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - The Worker. 1946 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - World Associatiuon of World Federalists. 1948-1966 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - World Constitution. 1948 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - World Council of Churches. 1945-1963 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - World Events, (Scott Nearing). 1946-1948 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - World Movement for World Federal Government. 1947-1950 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - World's Student Christian Federation. 1945-1947 (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - World Vision, Inc. 1956-1974 (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - World War II, air raid shelters. 1940-1942 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - World War II, APM re: war effort, civilian defense. 1942 (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - World War II, "Ballad for Americans." No Date (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - World War II, Civilian Defense Coordinating Council. 1942 (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - World War II, Civilian Protective Course. No Date (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - World War II, Miscellaneous. 1941-1942 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - World War II, Office of Facts and Figures. 1942 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - World War II, War Advertising Council. 1944-1946 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - World War II, War Department. 1942-1946 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - World War II, war ration book. No Date (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - world War II, wartime rodeo. No Date (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Writers Conference. 1949 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Writers Digest, article about APM and Letter. 1942-1946 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Writhers Digest (Larry Andrews). 1947-1950 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Writers Newsletter (Jessyca Russell). 1947-1948 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Writer's War Board (Rex Stout). 1942-1946 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Wycliffe Translators. 1967-1974 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous. 1942-1959 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Xerox. 1964-1971 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Yamamoto, Tomoko (befriended in relocation camp). 1942-1956 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Yankee Magazine. 1947-1956 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Yarnall, Eliz. Biddle (Mrs. Robert). 1944 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Yorck, Countess Ruth. 1947-1956 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Young Men's Christian Association. 1944-1973 (Box 75, Folder 20)